[sinister music playing]
-[Gon yelling] Why?
-[rumbling]
[aura exploding]
because it's not your fight.
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
The sunglasses guy
with the really big pipe,
you tag along with him, don't you?
You want him?
Then I suggest that you go out
and look for him.
[Cheetu] I know where he is,
but I can't get to him.
He controls smoke,
and he's hidden himself
behind a smoke screen,
and no matter how hard I try,
I just can't get through.
I scaled the roof
to see if I could get in from above.
Huh?
And I just so happened to spot you.
Ah, so I'm just a little warm-up
before you reach your real target.
I'm feeling very tired today.
Huh?
Let me have your ear for a moment.
For the very first time
Well, there'll be lots of time
for you to be shocked
when we're through.
[sighs]
Just how self-centered can you be?
Huh?
[Zeno] You know, if I were you,
I would keep a keen eye on my back.
[Cheetu laughs] Yeah, nice try.
[explosion]
Well…
looking wouldn't have helped you
all that much anyway.
[Silva] Would you have
preferred I spared him?
[Zeno] Hmm? Nah, not really.
[Silva] How's Killua doing?
[Zeno] Hmm? He's matured.
And I have reason to believe
he's removed Illumi's needle.
I had quite the bizarre experience.
You see, it felt as if
time was being condensed.
[Silva] I should take your stories
with a grain of salt, Dad.
[suspense music playing]
[Killua] Okay.
You and I should be safe here.
What's the update?
[exhales]
[Meleoron] God's Accomplice, deactivate.
Knuckle is gonna keep
running around, avoiding Youpi
to try and buy us more time.
He's out of his mind!
Okay.
What's the maximum time
you can use God's Accomplice?
The first time, I was so nervous
that I tapped out after just ten seconds,
but I've calmed down now.
I could go a full minute
if I don't have to move.
That's plenty,
'cause all I'm gonna need is one shot.
[narrator] Approximately three minutes
before Killua raised his finger…
Knuckle was in the air.
[narrator] Once, he punched out a cop
to help his friend escape
He was never caught.
[grunts]
[yelling]
[narrator] His ability
to maintain his stamina
while running at top speed
far outshines that of a cheetah.
[imperceptible]
Knuckle revealed his presence
to save Shoot
and focused his energy
on keeping his enemy distracted.
[Knuckle] He stopped chasing me?
[Knuckle] Damn. Shoot's in trouble.
Youpi could only assume
that the King
was still in the throne room.
Since he had been assigned
to keep watch over the staircase,
he also assumed that
two other Royal Guards, Pitou and Pouf,
were currently protecting the King.
This meant that his main priority
was to keep enemies
[gasps]
[Knuckle] Shoot!
[narrator] Shoot was still alive.
Shoot, I…
[somber music playing]
[Shoot groaning]
This guy doesn't even think that…
we're worth the effort to try
and kill off.
This was an unprecedented
insult to them both,
Are Shoot and I
nothing more than gnats to him?
Is that how it is?
Fine then,
but you're gonna regret it later,
because us gnats
are gonna make you go bankrupt
in about ten minutes!
Hey, Pouf and Pitou!
Hey, are you there?
[Knuckle] The boss used
Smoky Jail on the throne room.
That must mean that he and Pouf
are in there alone,
so the King is somewhere else.
[Menthuthuyoupi] Say something!
[groans] Damn it.
[Knuckle gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
[narrator] By the time
Knuckle realized
that he had made an error,
he had already made another one.
[Knuckle] Youpi's eyes
had met with Shoot's.
We knew death
was a possibility going in.
Shoot was right there,
[narrator]
When Knuckle imagined
the expression on Youpi's face
as he glanced
at the bloodied Shoot
and walked right past him
on his way to the third floor,
he realized that he had made
yet another error.
[Shoot] Damn it.
And why? For what reason?
For the world? For humanity?
There's no way in hell!
This is so unreal.
-[thudding]
-[Shoot groans]
[Shoot] I know that my job right now
should be to try and stop Knuckle.
"Are you crazy? Don't go."
"Just keep your mouth shut,
and buy more time."
That's what I should
be saying to him.
That son of a bitch,
the way he looked at me,
it was like… it was like…
I was nothing more than trash!
[crying] When you find him…
punch that bastard for me!
Yeah. I got this.
Sorry, Master,
Some things are more important
than saving the world.
[narrator] A brand-new error,
the significance
of something important.
[suspense music playing]
Answer me!
[Morel] Is that Youpi?
No way.
Did Shoot and Knuckle get killed?
I hope the old man's doing okay.
We thought we knew
what we were dealing with,
but these Royal Guards,
did we miscalculate?
I thought our plan
was actually working.
despite these emotions,
the ratio of his conviction
remains unchanged.
Just as I would expect
from a strong warrior.
I'm impressed.
However, that constraint
will be what inhibits
your decision making.
[Menthuthuyoupi] Damn it.
Why the hell is Pitou's En gone?
What happened? What's going on?
Shut up!
[rock music playing]
[Menthuthuyoupi]
The fuzz on my shoulder
But right now,
I have to find the King.
What the hell is going on?
It's pissing me off!
Okay, I've had enough!
What is it with you guys?
It was drastic enough
to make Knuckle
instantly turn to flee,
[Shoot groans]
Just hang on.
[Shoot] Did you get him?
Huh?
[narrator] Being under
extreme mental stress
that the true nature
of his ability was in truth
as well as his aura,
become engorged
with his furious rage.
The destruction that was unleashed
was accompanied
by intense pleasure.
Then, as he rapidly deflated,
he was overcome
by a sense of great loss.
Having had more experience,
Knuckle instantly understood
what had happened to Youpi.
I doubt it'll be easy
to goad him into doing that
on purpose
and still make it out unharmed.
It's high-risk, no doubt about it,
but it's an even higher return.
I'll make him mad so he blows up.
I need to get a strike in,
and that'll create
the perfect opportunity,
was close to perfect
for defeating Youpi.
Youpi was trying
desperately to figure out
how to utilize
this self-indulgent ability
in a way that would better
benefit the King.
[Menthuthuyoupi]
The best way I can think of
to serve the King
is to control this fury
without being consumed by emotion.
In other words,
the risks were incredibly high.
Three minutes have passed
since the mission began.
[sentimental music playing]
[narrator] Everyone's motives
were beginning to merge.
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "A False Rage."
[Killua] Yeah? Well, I don't care.
[Gon] Sorry, Killua.
[Killua] I'll never forgive you.
[Gon] Here, have a Choco Robo!
[Killua] Forgiven!
[singer singing in Japanese]